YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT SEEMS LIKE
ALL OF A SUDDEN
SO MUCH IS HAPPENING.
I KNOW. ROSS IS
GETTING MARRIED...
PHOEBE'S... MAKING PEOPLE.
EVERYBODY'S DOING STUFF.
AND WE JUST SIT HERE.
IF I DIED, THE ONLY WAY
PEOPLE WOULD EVEN KNOW
THAT I WAS HERE
WOULD BE BY THE ASS PRINT
ON THIS CHAIR.
LOOK, WE HAVE
TO DO SOMETHING, OKAY?
SOMETHING HUGE.
( snaps finger )
WE COULD CLIMB MT. EVEREST.
NO. NOT SOMETHING STUPID--
SOMETHING HUGE.
NO, NO, I SAW AN AD
FOR THIS VIDEO.
PEOPLE CLIMB THAT THING
EVERY DAY.
WE COULD TOTALLY DO THAT.
WHY NOT? I MEAN, IT'S JUST...
IT'S JUST CLIMBING.
IT'S JUST... IT'S JUST STEEP.
YEAH.
WE'RE GOING TO EVEREST, OKAY?
IT'D BE NICE TO LEAVE
AN ASS PRINT ON EVEREST.
HEY.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
WE'RE GOING TO CLIMB
MT. EVEREST.
YEAH, BABY!
REALLY.
I LOOKED INTO THAT.
YEAH, BUT I MEAN, IT COSTS,
LIKE, $60,000
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU COULD DIE
AND... YOU WOULD DIE.
OH... WELL.
WE COULD GET
THAT EVEREST VIDEO THOUGH.
YEAH, WE COULD DO THAT
WITHOUT, YOU KNOW,
RISKING OUR LIVES AT ALL.
AND WHILE WE'RE DOWN
AT THE VIDEO STORE
YOU KNOW
WHAT ELSE WE COULD RENT?
DIE HARD.
OH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST REMEMBERED
THAT EVEREST THING
IS ONLY AVAILABLE
THROUGH MAIL ORDER.
OH, WELL.
SO YOU GUYS WILL STAY HERE
AND HANG OUT WITH ME?
YEAH.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
ONE OF THESE DAYS,
WE'RE GOING TO GET OFF OUR BUTTS
AND RENT DIE HARD AGAIN.
YEAH, WE ARE!
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
SO WHAT DID WE DECIDE?
DOES YOUR UNCLE NATHAN
GET AN INVITE OR NOT?
OH, GOD, NOBODY
LIKES HIM.
AND HE'S SO CHEAP.
I MEAN, HE'D NEVER FLY TO
LONDON IN A MILLION YEARS.
YEAH, INVITE HIM.
HEY, DID I DO THESE
NEAT ENOUGH?
YEAH. THEY'RE FINE.
YEAH?
IF ANYONE ASKS
WE'LL SAY THAT BEN
ADDRESSED THEM.
( chuckles )
OH. SO YOU INVITED
RACHEL, THEN?
SURE. WHY NOT?
REALLY?
YEAH.
WELL, DON'T THINK
I'D BE COMFORTABLE
HAVING ANY OF
MY OLD LOVERS THERE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
DO YOU THINK MAYBE WE
SHOULDN'T INVITE HER?
OH, NO, NO, ROSS.
YOU KNOW I ABSOLUTELY
ADORE RACHEL.
IT'S JUST THAT...
WELL, I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE
A BIT AWKWARD FOR YOU.
BUT IT'S ABSOLUTELY
YOUR DECISION.
MORE TEA?
YEAH, SURE.
EARL GREY?
HUH? FINE.
INVITE WHOEVER YOU WANT.
I DON'T WANT TO
BE SINGLE, OKAY?
I JUST, I JUST,
I JUST WANT
TO BE MARRIED AGAIN.
AND I JUST WANT
A MILLION DOLLARS!
RACHEL?
OH, GOD, MONICA, HI.
THANK GOD.
Monica:
OKAY, EVERYBODY...
THIS IS RACHEL,
ANOTHER LINCOLN
HIGH SURVIVOR.
THIS IS EVERYBODY.
THIS IS CHANDLER
AND PHOEBE
AND JOEY AND...
YOU REMEMBER
MY BROTHER ROSS?
SURE!
HEY.
HI. OH!
OH, GOD!
YOU KNOW, YOU PROBABLY
DIDN'T KNOW THIS
BUT BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL,
I HAD A, UM...
MAJOR CRUSH ON YOU.
I KNEW.
YOU DID? OH.
( chuckles )
I ALWAYS FIGURED
YOU JUST THOUGHT
I WAS MONICA'S
GEEKY OLDER BROTHER.
I DID.
OH!
LISTEN, DO YOU THINK...
I TRY NOT TO LET
MY INTENSE VULNERABILITY
BECOME ANY KIND
OF A FACTOR HERE.
BUT DO YOU THINK
IT WOULD BE OKAY
IF I ASKED YOU OUT
SOMETIME, MAYBE?
YEAH.
MAYBE.
OKAY.
OKAY, MAYBE I WILL.
SEE, I SEE, UH...
BIG PASSION IN YOUR FUTURE.
REALLY?
I DO.
OH, ROSS,
YOU'RE SO GREAT.
OH...
AH...
IT'S NEVER GOING
TO HAPPEN.
YEAH, I'VE A QUESTION.
LOOK, UH, ACTUALLY,
NOT SO MUCH A QUESTION
AS MORE OF A GENERAL
WONDERING...
...MENT.
OKAY?
OKAY.
UM, WELL, FOR A WHILE NOW,
I'VE BEEN WANTING TO, UM...
OH...
YES, YES.
THAT'S-THAT'S RIGHT.
LOOK AT
THAT LITTLE KITTY!
WHAT?
( screaming )
♪ TOP OF THE WORLD LOOKIN' ♪
♪ DOWN ON CREATION ♪
♪ AND THE ONLY EXPLANATION ♪
♪ I CAN FIND... ♪
LISTEN, IF YOU
WANT THIS CART
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO TAKE ME WITH IT!
YES!
DID YOU SEE THAT!?
YOU WERE INCREDIBLE!
A BRAND-NEW WOMAN,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
I COULD NOT HAVE
DONE THIS WITHOUT YOU.
NO, IT'S JUST...
OKAY, UM, UH...
MORE CLOTHES
IN THE DRYER?
OH!
I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
YOU HAVE NO RIGHT
TO TELL ME
YOU EVER HAD
FEELINGS FOR ME.
WHAT?
I WAS DOING GREAT
WITH JULIE
BEFORE I FOUND OUT
ABOUT YOU.
I WAS DOING GREAT
BEFORE I FOUND OUT ABOUT YOU.
YOU THINK IT'S EASY FOR ME
TO SEE YOU WITH JULIE?
THE POINT IS, I...
I DON'T NEED THIS RIGHT NOW.
OKAY? IT'S-IT'S
TOO LATE.
I'M SOMEBODY ELSE;
I'M HAPPY.
THIS SHIP HAS SAILED.
FINE. GO AND DO THAT.
FINE. FINE.
I DON'T NEED YOUR STUPID SHIP!
GOOD.
OH!
( exasperated sigh )
( sobbing )
ROSS, DO YOU REALIZE
THIS IS
THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE
I'M DOING SOMETHING
I ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT?
THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME IN MY LIFE
I'M DOING SOMETHING
I'M ACTUALLY GOOD AT?
IF YOU DON'T GET THAT...
I GET THAT BIG TIME,
AND I'M HAPPY FOR YOU
BUT I'M TIRED
OF HAVING A RELATIONSHIP
WITH YOUR
ANSWERING MACHINE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
LOOK, NEITHER DO I!
IS THIS ABOUT MARK?
( exasperated sigh )
OH, MY GOD!
OKAY, IT'S NOT.
I CANNOT KEEP HAVING
THIS SAME FIGHT
OVER AND OVER AGAIN, ROSS.
NO, YOU'RE MAKING THIS TOO HARD!
I'M MAKING THIS TOO HARD?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW!
LOOK, MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST TAKE A BREAK.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S TAKE A BREAK.
LET'S COOL OFF, OKAY?
LET'S GET SOME FROZEN YOGURT
OR SOMETHING.
NO...
( sighs )
A BREAK FROM US.
DO I KNOW WHY
WE'RE RUSHING?
YEAH. YOU KNOW
THE GIRLFRIEND
I TOLD YOU ABOUT
LAST NIGHT?
WELL, IT TURNS OUT
THAT SHE WANTS TO GET BACK
TOGETHER WITH ME...
OH, I FOUND IT!
THAT'S SO GREAT
FOR YOU GUYS!
YEAH.
GOOD LUCK
WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
OH, THANK YOU.
I... HEY!
( giggling )
RACHEL!
HI!
OH... YOU GOT
MY MESSAGE, HUH?
YEAH. OH, YOU
ARE RIGHT ON TIME!
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY--
CAN I BE YOUR GIRLFRIEND AGAIN?
YES, YOU CAN,
VERY MUCH.
AH...!
I WANT YOU TO LEAVE.
JUST GET OUT!
I WANT TO STAY.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
ALL RIGHT. HOW WAS SHE?
UH-OH.
WH-WHAT?
WAS SHE GOOD?
DON'T ANSWER THAT.
COME ON, ROSS, YOU SAID YOU
WANTED TO TALK TO TALK ABOUT IT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT IT.
HOW WAS SHE?
SHE WAS...
AWFUL.
HORRIBLE.
NOT GOOD.
NOTHING
COMPARED TO YOU.
SHE WAS DIFFERENT.
UH-OH!
OOH!
GOOD DIFFERENT?
NOBODY LIKES CHANGE.
I...
JUST STOP THAT!
WHAT? OKAY! OKAY!
THE WAY YOU OWNED UP
TO EVERYTHING
IT JUST SHOWED ME HOW MUCH
YOU'VE GROWN, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, MY MOM NEVER
THOUGHT THIS WOULD WORK OUT.
( mirthless chuckle )
SHE WAS ALL,
"ONCE A CHEATER,
ALWAYS A CHEATER."
MM-HMM.
OH... I JUST WISH
WE HADN'T LOST
THOSE FOUR MONTHS.
BUT IF TIME IS
WHAT YOU NEEDED
JUST TO GET A LITTLE
PERS-PEC-TIVE...
THAT'S...
( shouting ):
WE WERE ON A BREAK!
YOU SEEM TO
REALLY LIKE HER.
YEAH, BUT WHAT AM I
GOING TO DO?
WE BOTH AGREED
IT WAS GOING TO BE
A TWO-WEEK THING, YOU KNOW--
NO COMMITMENT.
ROSS, THAT GIRL JUST SPENT
THE ENTIRE EVENING
TALKING TO YOUR FRIENDS,
ASKING TO HEAR
STORIES ABOUT YOU,
LOOKING THROUGH
MONICA'S PHOTO ALBUMS...
I MEAN,
YOU DON'T DO THAT
IF YOU'RE JUST IN IT
FOR TWO WEEKS.
YOU THINK? HUH.
YOU'VE GOT,
LIKE, 14 HOURS
UNTIL SHE HAS
TO BE AT THE AIRPORT
AND YOU'RE SITTING HERE
IN THE HALLWAY WITH A...
28-YEAR-OLD CHEERLEADER
WITH A FAT LIP.
( chuckles )
HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH.
( mailbox door closes )
OH, THIS IS
SO AMAZING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
MY BROTHER'S GETTING MARRIED
AND IN LONDON.
I MEAN, IT'S SO ROMANTIC.
HEY, PRETTY SMART.
TISSUE PAPER.
YOU'RE AT THE WEDDING,
YOU HAVE TO CRY...
"HANDKERCHIEF?"
"NO. I GOT MY INVITATION."
OH, LOOK!
ISN'T THIS ADORABLE?
ROSS LET BEN ADDRESS MINE.
HELLO.
All:
HEY.
HEY, DID YOU GET YOUR INVITATION
TO ROSS'S WEDDING?
NO.
WELL, DON'T WORRY, MAN.
I GET TO BRING A GUEST.
WE'LL SHOW HIM.
SO JEALOUS YOU'RE ALL GOING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I NEVER KNEW
YOU CAN'T FLY
IN YOUR THIRD TRIMESTER.
I DIDN'T KNOW EITHER.
I KNEW THAT.
SO I DIDN'T KNOW THAT
( chuckling ):
BUT YOU SHOULD
SEE YOUR FACES.
HI, GUYS. WHAT'S UP?
HEY.
WE'RE HANGING OUT.
WHAT'S THIS?
IS THIS
ROSS'S WEDDING INVITATION?
SEE, MAYBE THAT'S THE ONE
WE SHOULD HAVE ACTUALLY HIDDEN.
OH, NO, NO. GUYS, COME ON.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO THAT.
I'M HAPPY FOR HIM.
I AM. I REALLY... I'M... I...
I'LL WORK ON IT.
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
MMM.
RACHEL, YOU'RE GOING
TO COME THOUGH, AREN'T YOU?
OH, HONEY
I DON'T KNOW. I...
THIS ISN'T ONE
OF THOSE, YOU KNOW
"SHE DOESN'T COME,
WE DON'T COME," RIGHT?
BECAUSE I ALREADY
BOUGHT MY TICKET...
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE
REAL WEIRD...
IS IF YOU WEREN'T THERE.
JUST SAY YOU'LL THINK
ABOUT IT, OKAY?
NO, I'LL THINK
ABOUT IT. YEAH.
WHO'S THIS FROM?
OH, THAT'S ROSS'S.
OH.
( clears throat )
OH, MY GOD.
HE REMEMBERED!
REMEMBERED WHAT?
IT WAS LIKE MONTHS AGO.
WE WERE WALKING BY
THIS ANTIQUE STORE
AND I SAW THIS PIN
IN THE WINDOW
AND I TOLD THEM
THAT IT WAS JUST LIKE
ONE MY GRANDMOTHER HAD
WHEN I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE REMEMBERED.
THIS MUST HAVE COST HIM
A FORTUNE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE DID THIS.
ROSS? REMEMBER
BACK IN COLLEGE
WHEN HE FELL
IN LOVE WITH CAROL
AND BOUGHT HER THAT
RIDICULOUSLY EXPENSIVE
CRYSTAL DUCK?
WHAT DID YOU
JUST SAY?
( mumbling )
OH... MY GOD.
Announcer:
Flight 457
from Beijing now arriving.
OH, MY GOD.
ROSS AND I
WERE IN GRAD SCHOOL.
Ross:
WE HAVEN'T SEEN
EACH OTHER
SINCE THEN.
WELL, I LAND IN CHINA.
GUESS WHO'S IN CHARGE
OF THE DIG.
JULIE!
JULIE, ISN'T
THAT GREAT?
I MEAN, ISN'T THAT JUST
KICK-YOU-IN-THE-CROTCH,
SPIT-ON-YOUR-NECK FANTASTIC?
OH, THAT IS SO SWEET.
NO...
( chuckles )
NO, OKAY.
NO, YOU HANG UP.
NO, YOU... OKAY.
OKAY.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
WELL, YOU DIDN'T
HANG UP EITHER.
SHE DIDN'T HANG UP.
OKAY, NO. NO,
YOU HANG UP.
YOU, YOU, YOU...
ROSS?
HI. IT'S RACHEL.
I'M JUST CALLING TO SAY
THAT, UM, EVERYTHING'S FINE
AND I'M REALLY HAPPY
FOR YOU
AND YOUR CAT.
SO, OBVIOUSLY, I AM OVER YOU.
I AM OVER YOU
AND THAT, MY FRIEND,
IS WHAT THEY CALL "CLOSURE."
RACHEL, GOT A MESSAGE FROM YOU.
OH, MY GOD, ROSS, NO.
HANG UP THE PHONE.
GIVE ME THE PHONE.
GIVE ME THE
GODDAMNED PHONE!
GIVE ME THE PHONE.
YOU'RE OVER ME?
OH, GOD.
WHAT, YOU'RE, UH...
Y-YOU'RE OVER ME?
WHEN WERE YOU...
UNDER ME?
BASICALLY...
( clears throat )
LATELY, I'VE, UH...
I'VE, UH, SORT OF
HAD FEELINGS FOR YOU.
OKAY, I NEED TO LIE DOWN.
HE BROKE UP
WITH JULIE.
( chuckles )
WELL, GO HUG HER,
FOR GOD'S SAKES!
REALLY?
REALLY.
IT'S ALWAYS
BEEN YOU, RACH.
OH, GOD.
OH...
LISTEN, I'M SORRY,
I HAD TO WORK TONIGHT.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
YOU WERE WORTH THE WAIT.
OH.
AND I DON'T JUST
MEAN TONIGHT.
♪ I NEVER DREAMED ♪
♪ THAT I'D MEET
SOMEBODY LIKE YOU ♪
♪ I NEVER DREAMED ♪
♪ THAT I'D LOVE SOMEBODY... ♪
WHAT... AH...
♪ NO, I... ♪
♪ DON'T WANNA FALL IN LOVE ♪
♪ A WICKED GAME WE PLAY... ♪
OH, GOD!
OH, HONEY...
OH, IT'S OKAY.
OH, NO, YOU JUST ROLLED
OVER THE JUICE BOX.
GUNTHER, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING TO RACHEL
ABOUT ME AND THE GIRL
FROM THE COPY PLACE.
I'M SORRY.
WAS I NOT SUPPOSED TO?
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO ENDED IT, REMEMBER?
YEAH, BECAUSE I WAS MAD AT YOU
NOT BECAUSE
I STOPPED LOVING YOU.
YOU STILL LOVE ME?
NO.
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
WHAT ARE YOU...?
DO YOU WANT TO...
GET BACK TOGETHER?
NO... MAYBE.
I DON'T...
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST... I FEEL...
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I EVEN THOUGHT
OF GETTING BACK TOGETHER
WITH YOU.
WE ARE SO OVER!
( choked up ):
OH... OH... UH...
FINE BY ME!
AND HEY, JUST SO YOU KNOW
IT'S NOT THAT COMMON
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN
TO EVERY GUY
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL!
I KNEW IT!
Rachel's coming out.
Doesn't she
look pretty, Jack?
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS US GETTING READY
FOR THE PROM.
OH!
WE DON'T HAVE TO WATCH THIS.
YEAH, WE DO.
COME ON! COME ON!
Judy:
Get a shot
of Monica.
Jack:
WAIT. HOW DO YOU
ZOOM OUT?
THERE SHE IS.
WHOA!
SHUT UP!
THE CAMERA ADDS TEN POUNDS.
SO, HOW MANY CAMERAS
ARE ACTUALLY ON YOU?
Monica:
Dad, turn it off!
Jack:
IT IS OFF.
IT'S NOT.
Jack:
RIGHT, ROSS?
OH, COME ON.
LOOKING GOOD,
MR. KOTTER.
I CAN'T GO TO MY OWN PROM
WITHOUT A DATE.
I CAN'T.
IT'S TOO LATE.
IF YOU'RE NOT GOING,
I DON'T WANT TO GO EITHER.
I HAVE
A WONDERFUL IDEA.
YOU SHOULD TAKE RACHEL
TO THE PROM.
WE'VE SEEN ENOUGH.
LET'S TURN IT OFF.
NO, NO,
I WANT TO SEE.
WELL, I'M NOT GOING
TO WATCH.
Jack:
Come on, kid.
LET'S GO.
Judy:
ARE YOU HANDSOME.
Jack:
LET'S SHOW 'EM!
( nervous chuckle )
OKAY, DAD.
RACHEL, READY OR NOT
HERE COMES
YOUR KNIGHT IN SHINING...
OH, NO.
BYE! DON'T WAIT UP!
OKAY, CHIP!
LET'S GO.
Judy:
OH, DEAR.
JACK, HOW DO I TURN THIS OFF?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THAT.
YEAH, WELL...
SEE? HE'S HER LOBSTER.
NO!
YOU'RE REALLY NOT GOING?
YEAH.
IT'S JUST GOING
TO BE TOO HARD.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN,
IT'S ROSS.
HOW CAN I WATCH
HIM GET MARRIED?
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST,
IT'S FOR THE BEST,
YOU KNOW?
IT IS. IT'S...
PLUS, SOMEBODY'S GOT TO
STAY HERE WITH PHOEBE.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S GOING
TO PRETTY BIG BY THEN
AND SHE'LL NEED SOMEONE
TO HELP HER TIE HER SHOES.
DRIVE HER
TO THE HOSPITAL
IN CASE SHE GOES
INTO LABOR...
YOU DON'T HAVE A CAR,
AND YOUR LICENSE EXPIRED.
I KNOW.
YEAH, SEE, THERE'S
SO MUCH TO DO
AND I HAVE SO LITTLE
TIME TO DO IT IN.
ALL RIGHT, CHECK IT OUT.
CHECK THIS OUT.
SAYS HERE
THERE'S A PLACE YOU CAN GO
TO RENT VIDEOS
OF ALL THE MUSEUMS.
"IT'S ALMOST
AS GOOD AS BEING THERE."
IT'S BETTER.
YOU CAN'T GO TO A MUSEUM
IN YOUR UNDERWEAR.
WELL, YOU COULD,
BUT PROBABLY JUST THE ONE TIME.
I BET WE COULD
GET VIDEOS OF
ALL THE SIGHTS.
GET A VCR IN A HOTEL ROOM
WE'D NEVER EVEN HAVE
TO GO OUTSIDE.
IF WE DO THAT,
WE'VE GOT TO RENT DIE HARD.
OH-HO, I BET
THE BRITISH VERSION IS GOOD.